Made in ABC
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
No, it's just...
What are you doing?
It's like I'm on the edge of a cliff.
It's like I'm on a cliff.
It's stupid.
You know, what a tutor should do.
That's what a tutor should do, isn't it?
What's a tutor's job?
What do you think it is?
I'm listening to you.
I'm listening.
You're not listening, are you?
Which is more important, the smartphone or me?
Is it important to be a teacher?
I'm so lazy right now.
Do you want to do something?
If possible, I want to be a carpaccio or a shrimp gratin.
By the way,
such as the road signs of life and human formation.
The most important thing is class.
Class, class.
Rio, Rio, Rio.
What?
You had a class, right?
Why are you laughing?
Because it's interesting.
It's a very clear theory.
It's too simple.
Are you making fun of me?
I'm from Itenawase.
Shut up.
What happened?
What do you think of this?
Come on, come on, come on.
Carpaccio.
This is a convenience store.
This is it.
Why don't you call a teacher at school?
Mr. Sasaoka.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask you a question.
Do you know Komura, a second-year student of class C?
No, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
I can't get in touch with Mr. Toshishima.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
Actually, Komura ate at the convenience store.
I said I didn't know.
I'm busy preparing for the class.
I'm busy preparing for the entrance ceremony.
I'm busy.
I don't have a partner, but it's hard.
I have a lot of work to do.
That's not it.
That's Kyoto.
You should go.
I don't know that student.
What did you do?
Can I ask you a favor?
I can't get my hands off him.
I understand.
Thank you.
Mr. Sasaoka is a young man.
He's a student first.
He's great.
I'm not a mother.
I'm honest and cute.
Calm down.
Chocolate brownie.
I knew it.
I went to the convenience store.
I went.
I was told to go.
I don't understand.
Why am I angry?
I should have contacted the police.
I went to the convenience store.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sweating?
Are you worried?
I ran into you.
You're a basketball player.
The store manager is a bad guy.
He's a criminal.
He's a cop.
He shouldn't do that.
Didn't you learn it at school?
Didn't you learn it?
What kind of education do you have?
You don't teach?
Don't you teach that you're a criminal?
I don't teach.
You should have told your parents.
What about the police?
I'll watch a lot this time.
Don't call me.
I'm in danger.
Look at me.
I'm a good student.
You don't know which side you're on.
That's terrible.
In the old days, all the students were good students.
But these days, they dye their hair and wear clothes.
You don't even wear a uniform.
Why are you wearing a jersey?
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm on vacation.
I'm sorry.
I know that.
What's wrong with wearing a jersey on vacation?
I'm sorry.
I want to say that the students these days are bad.
What?
What is this?
Is this because of the teacher?
Is the school desperate for students?
I'm sorry.
Don't you have pride in your school?
What?
It can't be helped for a young teacher like you.
There are too many things to say.
The comments are in my head.
You're the one who says that.
I can wear it.
Kumura is depressed.
What about his parents?
I didn't tell them.
They told me not to tell them because it was a request.
They said there was no one at home.
Did he feel lonely?
I wonder if he feels lonely.
Do you want to eat something before you go home?
Is that okay?
There's no one after you get home, right?
Yeah.
Today is a special day.
It's okay.
I'll feed you.
I'm sorry.
There's a restaurant called Yoshihiro.
What do you think?
I like the restaurant, too.
I've always wanted to go there.
Where?
I want to eat sushi.
I want to eat sushi that hasn't been served yet.
I'll have tuna.
I'll have tuna and salmon roe.
Okay.
I'll have the bill, please.
The bill is 12,000 yen.
I don't care about the bill.
I don't need your refreshing smile.
I'm angry.
It's poison.
You paid for it, didn't you?
I paid for it.
Why did I pay for it?
You should have paid for it.
It hurts.
12,000 yen.
Don't do that.
You keep saying that.
I'm going to hunt eggs.
That's a security bill.
What?
It's a necessary security bill.
You can reduce the cost of construction.
Is that so in the whole world?
Is the whole world a heaven?
You can't think of that as a salaryman.
I want to quit.
I want to quit teaching.
Good morning.
You're early today.
Didn't you go?
What?
I heard that you're going to be on TV.
You're going to be on TV?
That's great.
That's right.
I heard you're going to interview the president.
You've been doing well lately.
Sorry.
The bathroom is open.
You can do a lot of things with your father's company.
That's right.
I'm going to eat.
Dad, can you send me to school?
Sure.
Can I go to the station?
I'm going to the bathroom.
By the way, where is my sister's bathroom today?
What?
Rio, I feel like quitting.
I finally made up my mind to quit.
Really?
What?
I just saw it.
My sister's.
What?
You saw it next to me?
Yes.
I finally made up my mind to quit.
Really?
Really.
You're so funny.
You're going to the bathroom?
Yes.
I see.
What's wrong?
Dad, can you give me some advice next time?
Sure.
It's a holiday, but it's hard every day.
Me?
Seri is a circle.
Please come in.
Excuse me.
I need to talk to you.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Sure.
Director.
I'm in charge.
Sure.
I'd like to ask for a third-year C-class partner from the new semester.
What?
I'm sorry for the sudden request.
Well, I don't have a lot of understanding.
But the second-year C-class partner...
You're talking about Mr. Toyoshima, right?
Yes.
Actually, Mr. Toyoshima was hospitalized the other day.
He was hospitalized?
He met with a car accident on Ginza Street.
He didn't make it to the hospital, but it was a big accident.
I was wondering if I could ask Mr. Sasaoka for a third-year partner from the new semester.
No.
I agree.
If I were Mr. Sasaoka, I would react the same way.
But I'd like you to do your best.
I'll follow you as much as I can.
I can't say no to this situation.
So what's Mr. Sasaoka talking about?
There's no way I can say it.
What is it?
Mr. Sasaoka is asking me for a third-year partner.
I'm so worried about him.
Mr. Sasaoka.
Yes.
Are you Mr. Sasaoka?
Nice to meet you. I'm Kaito Yamazaki.
I'm in charge of English.
Nice to meet you.
I heard you're going to be a third-year partner.
I'm a little nervous.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
And then...
I got fired.
You shouldn't have quit.
It can't be helped.
You should have done what I told you when you got a job.
I can't watch it.
It's early in the morning and late at night.
If you don't want to be a third-year partner,
you have to prepare for the class.
What if you don't want to be a third-year partner?
It's just a bad feeling to say such a negative thing to a person who decided to do it.
What if you try too hard?
It's not funny.
I'll talk to the school.
At least let me be the third-year partner.
The teacher's parents don't want to go to school.
It's impossible for the teacher's parents to be a monster parent.
There's a teacher's problem.
Really?
Really.
You're too much of a face-to-face parent.
Face-to-face parent?
Face-to-face?
I won't say that.
I'm serious.
My son is sick, so I'll let him rest.
Really?
Really.
From the teacher's parents?
From the teacher's parents.
You're good at reading.
I'm not close.
I'm good at reading.
That's what you say.
Really?
Really.
Oh, my!
What are you talking about?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
What's going on here?
Good morning.
It's been a long time.
There are quite a few people who are on leave.
Hello.
I'm sure you've heard a lot of things.
I'm Ryo Sasaoka, a new member of this class.
Nice to meet you.
Ryo Sasaoka, a new member of this class
I'm a member of the basketball club.
I've met a few people and talked to them.
Ryo-chan.
I'm also a new member of the club.
I'm the new member, Mr. Kaito Yamazoe.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kaito Yamazoe.
I'm in charge of English.
Good morning, everybody.
It's always been my dream to become a teacher since I was small.
Let's make the best out of your final year in high school.
When I was in high school, I went to a national soccer tournament.
It was a scholarship.
I'm also a member of the soccer club.
By the way, how many soccer clubs are there in this class?
There are three in my class.
I'm a member of the soccer club.
Thank you.
Captain, are you Kenko Minami?
Yes, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Teacher, I want to change seats.
Change seats?
I want to change seats.
I'll go with you.
Ms. Sasaoka.
How was it?
I didn't do anything, but I'm tired.
This will be a good experience.
I think this is the start of the important step up in Ms. Sasaoka's career.
I think so too.
Good luck.
Thank you.
You don't have to work hard.
You're here.
Do you want to go a lot tonight?
I might die if I don't go.
Let's invite the new vice director.
That's right.
I can't drink.
You don't have to worry about it.
Thank you.
Welcome to the life of a teacher in hell.
And to the world of a person in need.
Cheers.
You're going with them.
Do you want to go instead?
I'm happy.
Are you happy too?
How was your first day as a single?
Everyone's eyes...
Everyone?
The students?
Yes.
I feel like I'm looking at something unacceptable.
Well, if your husband suddenly gets hospitalized,
it's going to be difficult for the students.
That's right.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
What kind of teacher was Mr. Toyoshima?
I think he was popular among the students.
He was very enthusiastic.
He was also popular among the teachers.
Was he okay?
Was he injured?
Yes.
I think he's going to retire.
It doesn't seem to be a serious injury,
but rather than an accident,
right?
Really?
Did he do it to himself?
Did he?
I think he was very mentally ill.
He doesn't know how to work, does he?
I don't think the school will admit it officially,
but there are as many idiots as teachers who work hard.
But this...
If it's the same distance as Mr. Toyoshima,
it means he's in trouble.
Mr. Toyoshima is a great teacher of training.
Even with that teacher,
he's showing that the class was in trouble.
Do you understand this case?
He's so stubborn.
Is it a class with a lot of problems?
That's right.
That's why I refused.
What?
Do your best.
I'll support you.
Please forgive me.
Is it next week already?
Yes.
I'm going to throw up just imagining it.
Security society.
I can't forgive you.
I can't forgive you, Mr. Goh.
The next day
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you for coming.
I'm going to work as a new manager.
My name is Rio Sasaoka.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
My name is Kaito Yamazoe.
I'm a freshman this year.
I'm a freshman.
I'm an English teacher.
I'll introduce myself in English.
Hello, everyone.
I am bright, fun, and passionate guy.
Although I'm still new here,
I will try my very best with positive energy.
Thank you.
First of all,
I'd like to choose a class member.
Your voice is too low.
Can anyone do it?
I'd like to choose a class member.
Akamatsu-san.
Akamatsu-san lives nearby.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask someone else.
I understand.
Thank you.
Mr. Kiyota, are you a private assistant?
That's personal information.
The student card says Murphy on the top right.
I'm sorry.
That's all.
Do you have any questions?
Are you all right?
Excuse me.
Yes.
I don't know what to say.
It's too late.
Does it mean that you will always be a private assistant?
What do you mean?
I think it's a burden to leave the last important time of the third year to such a young teacher.
Please be confident.
It's a big problem whether you can leave the child alone or not.
It's the most important time of the life.
I think my child will get a job.
Can you take responsibility for the job?
I've heard that it's important how many pipes you have in various companies.
Toyoshima-sensei was relieved because he heard that he was very good at getting a job.
That's right.
Mr. Fukutan.
Yes.
You greeted us in English, but we didn't come to see the entertainment show.
That was fun.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I don't know what to say about this.
I saw Mr. Sasaoka the other day.
He went to that fancy restaurant in Okachimachi, Akihabara.
That's right.
He was buying underwear at the select shop there.
Well, what's that?
I don't know what to say, but I was wondering what it would be like as a teacher.
He was buying a pretty flashy underwear.
How can a teacher wear that kind of underwear?
What if he was buying underwear for children?
What are you going to explain to him?
Well...
That's...
Speaking of that, I saw the teacher.
He was wearing a fancy underwear.
He was buying a lot of alcohol.
He was messing around with his boyfriend.
I don't care.
I don't care, but I can imagine what he would be like.
He was messing around with his boyfriend while drinking.
He was cheating on him.
He was telling his children not to drink and not to play around.
If he did that, he wouldn't be able to pass the test.
That's right.
Is that so?
What do you mean, is that so?
Yes.
Why don't you ask the experienced teacher to write it down?
Don't be ridiculous!
He's a teacher.
He's a human being.
You're destroying the power of a monster parent.
It's a monster for real.
It's impossible.
It's absolutely impossible.
I'm worried.
I'm going to ask my cute little daughter to write it down.
That's right.
That's what happens when you think it's important.
What are you talking about?
That's why it's called a monpe.
If you don't have common sense, you won't get the word monpe or kahogope.
It's called a kureima.
When you get excited to say what you want to say, you'll bring out a meaningless logic.
I don't think it's that bad.
It's not that bad.
That's a personal problem.
Why do you say that?
You were talking about the guardian and you were just pretending.
What?
You two were pretending not to understand.
I could see it.
Mr. Yamazoi was standing up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mr. Sasaoka was also there.
You were saying that.
You were pretending to say it.
That's because it's so unreasonable.
I cut off the lips of the claim.
I'm Komura's mother.
Really?
It's empty.
It's too empty.
It was this big.
When I was not a single person, I took off your son.
You didn't say it.
I can't say it.
There's no way I can say it.
You did your best.
It's okay, isn't it?
Even if you quit.
That's what I was going to do once.
I can't stand seeing you so stressed out.
You're always laughing.
I'm not.
If I don't laugh at Rio's mouth.
It's just going to fall into a loop.
The two of us.
Certainly.
You know.
Rio said he decided to quit last month.
I thought this was the time to make a decision.
No.
By the way.
Rio quit and became a single person.
It's harder than before.
I was completely missing the timing.
I was missing it.
Wait.
You're kidding me.
Open it.
I'll open it.
What should I do?
Really?
Please marry me.
Where are you going?
Rio hasn't answered yet.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
I'll make a mistake.
Can't you at least get rid of him?
That's why he's in the Z generation.
Dr. Nakamichi.
Oh, sorry.
I heard about you in the protection society.
Is that the reason?
Yes.
It's true.
I'm going to quit teaching if you do that.
What?
I understand.
Director.
I'm going to quit teaching if you do that.
But can you teach me a little longer?
No, I'm serious.
You can't force yourself to do what you don't want to do.
Then what should I do?
Can't you do something about it, Dr. Nakamichi?
No, I can't.
You can't do it even if you're tied up?
I'm going to assign a teacher to another business.
I'll do it.
Then I'll have to do it.
What?
Are you going to assign a teacher to another business?
That's all I can do.
I've never heard of it.
Looking at your sad face,
I'm ready to do it.
I've never heard of it.
I love the word, never heard of it.
I'm going to try something I've never done before.
But...
I won't be able to go to your family.
You should go.
My life as a single person ends here.
Are you going to quit teaching?
Yes.
I'll continue teaching, but as a single person...
I see.
Let's go.
I want to talk to you.
May I?
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Dr. Ryo.
What's wrong?
May I?
Dr. Ryo...
You said you liked cookies, didn't you?
She said she loved them to death.
When I first introduced myself.
I like them. I love them.
We're from the cooking department.
We just baked them.
They're freshly baked.
Why don't you give them a taste?
It's not a taste.
We baked them for you.
What's wrong?
Listen to Ryo.
It's not Ryo.
It's okay, Ryo.
Really?
I know everyone calls me that.
You found out.
What about me?
The cooking department.
My mom was amazing.
I was the worst.
Me too.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
I want you to get better.
Right?
This is an apology from your parents.
It's okay.
Why do your parents know about this?
Komura is at home.
I told Mr. Sasaoka to take care of him.
What?
He's so annoying.
It would be great if he could change now.
I wonder if Mr. Toshima will come back.
What did you say?
What?
What did you say to Sasaoka?
My parents are the worst.
They made fun of Sasaoka.
That's right.
But you don't really trust them.
We're the same age.
You're wrong.
What's wrong?
Sasaoka is a good guy.
Komura, you like Rio, don't you?
Shut up!
What's wrong?
It's not like that.
You're too young.
Actually, I...
I was caught on a holiday.
What?
Really?
I was contacted by the school.
I thought it was Toshima.
Sasaoka came.
I didn't know it was Toshima.
But he apologized for me many times.
He said there was no one at home.
He took me out to eat.
When he came back,
he said I was embarrassed to eat.
I was embarrassed.
So I didn't confess to him.
I didn't confess to him.
I shouldn't have let him quit.
I'm a good guy.
I want you to tell your parents.
I want you to tell them.
I don't want you to be like Toshima.
I want you to be like Toshima.
That's what happened.
I'm sorry.
Komura.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Teacher.
Don't quit.
It's been a long time since I've been in the bathroom.
I'm sorry.
I thought I'd do my best for another year.
I decided to see their graduation.
I'm looking forward to the wedding after that.
I wonder what my boyfriend will say.
The End
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm Ryo Sasaoka, a new member of this class.
We're from the cooking club.
We're here for you.